# **Aman Sharma**

### Web Developer

Hi there, I am Aman, just another creative geek. I have a very curious path both personally and professionally. Since I was a little boy, I've been fascinated by how we use technology and interact with things. After designing and developing for a couple of years during my graduation, , I am dedicatedly learning design and code on my own and have been working as a UI/UX designer and full-stack developer since past two years.. I need to learn many things and hungry to learn more and be more...





## **Personal Info**

#### Phone

7987199909

#### Address

Q-404 Abode Valley

#### E-mail

amansharma33.as@gmail.com

#### Date of birth

1996-07-09

#### www

officialaman.in

BOOTSTRAP



#### Skills

HTML	•••••
CSS	••••
JAVA SCRIPT	•••00
PHP	••••
MYSQL	••••
NODEJS	•••00
MONGODB	••••
WORDPRESS	••••
ANGULAR	•••00
MTERIAL DESIN	••••



### **Experience**

2015-05 - CDAC ACTS

2015-06 TRAINEE

As a trainee working in CDAC ACTS, the experience was good and gained an knowledge in core and advanced java.

2016-05 - TECHLECT BUSINESS AND SOLUTIONS

2016-06 INTERN

Done the internship for one month and worked on the complaint management system project using php and mysql.

2016-08 - SRM-ADT

present WEB DEVELOPER

Web developer under the directorate of engineering team. The experience

was quite good.

2016-12 - FIZZ FLYER

present WEB DEVELOPER

Fizz Flyer is an tours and travels startup and currently working as a web

developer under the team.



# Education

2014-05 - SRM UNIVERSITY

2018-05 Undergraduate degree in Software Engineering, working on various

projects mainly targeted at Data Structures, Optimization, Web

Development, Big data, Digital Image Processing. Currently holding a

CGPA of 8.7 till 5 semester.

2013-07 - BHAVANS PROMINENT

2014-07 Grade 12, Central Board of Secondary Education, graduated with 72%,

Majors include Physics, Chemistry and Maths.



2017-02 Facebook developer circles chennai

2017-03 Pay pal chennai